Bishawjit Kumar Dey

6900, Rue de Touraine, H1T3T2, Montréal, Canada, Phone : +1 778 636 3415, Email-bishawjit12@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/bishawjit-kumar-dey-a57511273

Customer Service Representative

Experienced customer service representative with seven years of experience of serving valued clients in a state-owned bank along with responsibilities that included overseeing cash counters, efficiently serving clients at the front desk in busy office environments along with the capability to establish and maintain excellent communication and relationships with valued clients.

Experience

Order Picker Clerk | Lufa Farms Distribution Center, Thimens Blvd Dec. 2023 – October-2024

- ⇒ Picked customer orders from the distribution center and processed delivery.
- ⇒ Efficient in Portioning
- ⇒ Received training and certification for distribution center activities.

Package Handler | FedEx Ground, Dorval

October 2023 – December 2023

- ⇒ Sorted and scanned packages
- ⇒ Loaded and unloaded packages from the trailer
- ⇒ Managed heavy lifting of packages upto 60 lbs.
- ⇒ Possess the ability to handle challenging physical tasks.

Kitchen Attendant / Noobox Restaurent, Palais Des Congres,

August 2023- September 2023

- ⇒ Served as kitchen attendant and cook.
- ⇒ Prepared a wide variety of oriental cuisines.

Senior Officer / Janata Bank Limited, Bangladesh

January 2015-June 2022

Supervised one stop service desk that provides all essential banking services to valued clients.

- ⇒ Opened a checking and savings account for walk-in clients.
- ⇒ Assisted customers with banking product information and inquiries.
- ⇒ Aided clients with familiarizing the bank's digital products and mobile apps.
- ⇒ Issued cheque books to clients.
- ⇒ Issued credit and debit cards to account holders.
- ⇒ Aided prospective clients with loan assessment.
- ⇒ Managed loan recovery and maintained communication with clients with irregular recovery history.
- ⇒ Having hands-on experience of core banking software e.g., Temenos T24 CBS.
- ⇒ Devised and executed promotional strategies to drive client engagement and business growth.

Skills

- Elegant written communication skill.
- Empathy and patience in dealing with customers.
- Ability to create and maintain long lasting client relationships.
- Capable of working independently and in a team environment and in a warehouse setting.
- Efficient in MS Office Suite.
- Comprehensive familiarity with Core Banking software such as Temenos T24.

Language Skills

- Fluent in English and Bengali.
- Scored a band score of 7.5 in International English Language Testing System (IELTS).

Academic Background

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)

2004-2011

Major in Management Information System Shahjalal University of Science and Technology, Sylhet, Bangladesh

Availability Schedule

Available throughout the week from 07.00h to 00.00h